foreign
awake again Sunday 6 p.m welcome to
Steve's place I'm glad to see everyone
here tonight
and um oh tonight's gonna be a little
bit different
um
I'm gonna talk a little bit about the
conference
and then I'm going to turn around and uh
I'm gonna play the video from uh burn
Ross presentation from 2005 which is
extremely interesting and it and if any
one of you have comments I go ahead and
send them in I'll try to answer them the
best that I can
anyway uh
I need to remind everyone first of all
we have the 2023 furnished technology
campus coming up
and um
I'm really hoping that it get a really
good attendance there we have quite a
few people signing up but we like to
have a lot more sun between now and then
uh
this is a live conference and the big
problem you know that we have that since
sakova is that people
uh have become isolated and they really
don't want to leave their houses and
that and um
and that leads to uh reduction in what
you can learn
the studies show that uh when we closed
down the schools and that our education
has fallen behind well the same thing
happens to us
as uh independent research is that if we
don't get out and meet enter mingle with
people face to face and sit and talk to
people and exchange ideas
um which is what the whole concept of
the conference was then
um
I'm always going to be isolated and
we're trying to break that isolation
down first and foremost with our
conferences which are live and uh
because they're live you have an
opportunity to meet people
talk to people
we have equipment there uh that would be
considered extraordinary you know
actually I'm thinking about renaming the
conference to be the disruptive
technology conference because the
technologies that we cover at our
conference would disrupt the status quo
as we know it you know imagine instead
of having all these um
all this chemical Rockets being shot up
by SpaceX and the uh and that's and that
they uh in order to work with a real
anti-gravity you know and polluting the
atmosphere so much you know
um and then also like a Bobby
on the medical side the hillside a lot
of the stuff is dismissed out of hand
um
a lot of stuff is dismissed out of hand
because it's so
well applies both to the people who
don't
really try things the biggest impediment
to progress is the ability to believe
that something is real our conference
people bring their equipment they
demonstrate it they show that this stuff
is real technology it actually works you
know
um
as time goes on I mean think about it
you know
in the 1800s now space flight you know
was a Fool's dream you know yet we have
just fine all over the place you know
Tesla demonstrate remote control and he
also demonstrated drones you know and
what do we have right now on the other
side of the world we're having an entire
War uh being based on a drone Warfare
you know
all this stuff was unimaginable you know
radio you know
you know all this stuff at one time
was a Fool's errand to believe in or
even think about but yet it's what's
driving
our our economy our society today yeah
so I encourage everyone to come to the
conference
um
because if I come to the conference you
get to see for yourself what's real and
what's not this is like a lot of real
stuff out there the conference is August
9th the 13th at the Crowne Plaza Hotel
and
an Albuquerque
and um
and uh we expect that well the rooms are
sims last year they started aging to
dollars they include
they include a breakfast and free Wi-Fi
and at night you know we have our uh our
evening the meals in there or actually
yeah
Refreshments or whatever but
they're pretty substantial you know and
we have different stuff like we have a
taco bar one night you know and we had
pizza bar on another we had fried
chicken we've had chicken wing bars now
so this is it's pretty good stuff you
know you won't start start that's for
sure
and um and it's and it provides an
opportunity for you to sit down as you
can see in the picture there and
actually uh meet with other people there
and I I think we have a pretty good
lineup I'm getting ready to mail out the
programs uh here probably in a week or
two and um
and if you if you need something to hand
out give me a call I can send you
another 10 or 15 uh programs if you want
you need that major go out and hand out
to other people I'd like people to help
us get people to come to this conference
this conference is important
um
outside of UFO conferences
there's nothing out there that really
life accomplishes that
that touch on what we touch on even uh
Aaron's conference up in Idaho uh he's
limited and how many people can have
there and he's focused on more having a
a video conference you know
and those are nice and then they give
some information out but there's nothing
like going and touching the equipment up
close you know and actually feeling that
stuff and seeing that it happens you
know and uh
and as far as like uh past conferences
we have over a thousand videos of past
conferences both as extraordinary
technology conference and the Exotic
research conferences are all up there
and we're working even last year's
conferences up there you have to be a
member to view the last year's
conference in the year before last but
uh for 9.99 a month you have access to a
thousand videos 24 7. you know and uh
it's like instantaneous you know you
know you don't have to order it and then
wait no to get into the mail or anything
and uh and so it's just great
and they're on YouTube and uh soon we'll
be doing the conference on free energy
soon
um so I encourage everyone to get up
there and uh sign up now
without further ado
I'm gonna introduce um
without further Ado we're gonna
turn it over to Vernon Roth from 2005
and uh Mike Riverstone unfortunately
there's no one with us we'll be doing
the uh the presentation
um are the introduction
so
so these Tesla
wrong one
okay
you have to excuse me I'm still learning
the soul system here
um maybe someday I'll be a real
professional at this stuff
and um and this stuff will be like uh
super fast
and if we could always use some help too
right now I want to be able to convert
some of our um
our videos into uh shorts but I don't
know how to do that
anyone does have an experience and
create a short from an mp4 I would love
to hear from you
and um
and without any further ado
here's Vernon Roth
these high spin elements are
conventional usually metallic
elements and this High spin corresponds
to the implosive force of nature we had
an extensive discussion about the
balance of explosion and implosion in
terms of research and so he's very up on
that
he's got expertise in linguistics and
also construction
he lives in Westcliffe Colorado right
now he's building his own Dome house and
he also used to be work as a criminal
youth counselor
and he was in the Wilderness at one
point for seven months straight which is
a pretty amazing thing in itself he
studied electronics and mechanical
design also studied psychology and
physics and he's come into alternative
medicine because of a situation with one
of his children and he's found that the
alternative medicine has really worked
in this situation he sells energized
water and other products and he's a good
example of a solid homegrown scientist
researcher I'm very happy to welcome
Vernon Roth
[Applause]
good afternoon ladies and gentlemen
the subject of my presentation today
I guess I'm not going yet there we go
the subject of my presentation today is
as you can see ancient technology meets
quantum physics
and it is going to I'm going to outline
the use of high spin elements
in the research me and the past present
and future and I'm going to start with
basically where I came from and how
these elements are utilized and such and
then give you some information on the
new technologies that are coming out
in regards to those elements
a little background about myself I
started college when I was very young
and
it was kind of an interesting uh
interesting time I was just a voracious
reader and I loved to study and learn
all sorts of new and interesting things
and so when I was studying in college I
actually was exposed to the work of T
Henry T Henry Murray and which was very
nice because eventually I was able to
actually meet one of the uh one of the
relatives of Murray's assistants and
learned some very interesting facts
about the gentleman
I studied the work of Ed gray and his
cold electricity devices
as well as Tom Barden scalar beams and
Fields now as I was studying in college
it was uh it was very interesting
because I would take the I would take
these ideas these phenomenal fantastic
ideas like uh cold electricity and I
would go to my my professors and say hey
can you tell me can you tell me about
this and they would kind of look at me
and say
I don't think you quite get it
um
electricity is not cold it's hot and no
there is no free electricity everything
is uh everything has losses everything
breaks down over time and so what I
realized was eventually that the
establishment does not always have the
answers and so I turned to organizations
like this and others to to start to
learn more about what is going on with
uh with different types of energy and
that kind of led me on this path and
it's been a phenomenal phenomenal path
eventually I was led to take a class can
I move around
okay great I was led to take a class in
physics because I was studying chemistry
at the time I assuming uh studying
psychology at the time and my sister
said I needed to take something in the
hard Sciences instead of uh instead of
you know the brain sciences and it was
very interesting it was in an auditorium
much like this in the physics professor
professor Gilbert who formerly of Los
Alamos NASA and the Apollo space program
he stood up there just like I'm standing
here now and he said something very
interesting
he said I'm going to tell you a story it
is a fiction story but it is the best
story that we have in the future the
story will change as it has in the past
if you disagree with this story please
feel free to write your own
now that was a very interesting
statement for me
and by this he was saying that not
everybody has the answers as I said
before the establishment doesn't always
have the answers if you feel like
there's a better answer out there do the
research
and come back and present it write to
your own story and so that's in a sense
what we're doing here today isn't it
we're redefining we're redefining
technology as we know it and it was a
very interesting time for me because
about halfway through the semester this
professor did in fact do just what he
said he threw out the textbook and said
I'm going to teach you things that
they're just barely writing about in the
physics journals themselves
and we went on to reproduce the the wave
versus particle reality experiments
utilizing lasers does is a laser photon
is it a wave is it a particle
is it going to go through door a or door
B
and this was a this was a very
interesting time for me because we were
actually like I said in an auditorium
like this reproducing quantum physics
experiments
and I came to a very interesting reality
realization is that thought controls
reality and yes the self-help gurus have
been saying this for a very long time
but here was quantum uh Quantum proof
that this was this was in fact a reality
and based on that
we can also discern that how you view a
problem controls the outcome so if the
established scientific Community is
saying well it's impossible to develop
anti-gravity or if it's impossible to
have free energy then it will always be
impossible for them
and so what we need to do is we need to
say
it is possible can I do this and it's
interesting because this has led me to
some very interesting people I have met
people that have created particle
accelerators in their backyards I have
met people that have developed cold
electricity literally you hold the bulb
in your hand it's burning cold and you
put it into water that was kind of a
freaky experience dipping your hand into
water and not having it electrocute you
and so the defining characteristic of
these people is that it can be done not
that it can't be done
let's just find a way to make it happen
so in my quest and as a
as uh the uh Larry mentioned as I was
getting uh introduced here uh my
daughter had was diagnosed recently with
CP cerebral palsy and this was actually
a quest to try and Define some way to
help her we didn't even know what was
going on we knew that there was some
type of neurological disorder and we the
uh community in the the medical
community was not able to help us
whatsoever until just bear just recently
once after she's almost six years old
and so
I was actually led to the field of
alternative archeology now this may
sound off the subject but it's not
really it it is quite quite on the
subject in the field of alternative
archeology there are several assumptions
that are made first of all we believe
that history many parts of history as we
know it are in fact false
they are
creations of people that uh that do not
remember actually what happened
and so
um one of the basic tenets of the uh
oops lights over here isn't it one of
the basic tenets of alternative
archeology is that we've discovered that
there are vast civilizations that
covered both this continent and other
places in the world that we have
absolutely no record of whatsoever we
have a few statues a few rocks with a
few few markings on it and that's it
that's all oops how did that happen I
didn't push the button
so I'm back thank you
um what we end what we have come to find
out as we study these these our ancient
archaeological sites is that there was
in fact a technology
that was vastly outside of our current
mode of understanding now we we believe
in electricity and we believe in
electron flow and whatever technology
these these civilizations utilize and
I'm not saying they're more advanced or
less advanced than we are I'm saying
that they are a different idea of
Technology it's outside of our current
mode of understanding
and lastly we we realize very quickly
that if through in-depth study of these
civilizations and their Technologies we
could in fact find out a deeper
understanding for our science and our
reality for instance we as we see here
this is the picture many of you have
probably seen it before of a Tesla coil
being energized inside of a pyramid and
look at the interesting symbol or shape
pattern that is coming out of the top of
that the double helix DNA strand this
right here is a skull cap found on found
in an Egyptian tomb and you'll notice
the circular serpent pattern intertwined
serpent pattern here on the screen now
this whole this right here
and this these shapes right here are
subject for a much much larger
discussion but it's enough to illustrate
the point that they had an understanding
that we have just barely come to in the
past 50 to 100 years
now taken one step further
we can see that our DNA strands which
look very similar to the you know I'm
not going to go backwards just in case
that look very similar to the patterns
on the caduceus coils the Mercury wands
and all all of the ancient writings
having to do with medicine
our DNA is very very similar to that
this right here is another subject of a
of a huge huge vast study this is
practically a three-dimensional version
of this broken down there are elements
of Phi harmonics there are elements of
global scaling or Universal scaling
depending on what continent you're on
this right here is is a field of study
that you could spend your life just
trying to understand the the extreme
depth of this but we're not going to go
into that we're going to go into this
here see this is my oldest daughter her
name is Sage
she's seven years old she wants to grow
up to be Laura Croft and I am fostering
that ambition as much as I can
she is sitting on an ancient Temple that
we found actually I'll let you in a
little secret it's actually near here
but it's pretty inaccessible
it's made out of a very interesting
Stone and I'm going to be demonstrating
that actually I'll take you to it right
now if we want to raise the lights a
little bit
what we have here is what we call a
Genesis Stone
and I'll be explaining what I mean by
that that stone that she is
okay that stone that she was sitting on
in another reality
okay fantastic that Stones those stones
that she are sitting on actually started
out as this very soft white stone
and became this rock hard crystalline
structure
these Stones as I'm going to show on
shows later on are in fact what are
known as type 3 superconductors
so it's very interesting that this
ancient civilization would build an
entire Temple a seven-tiered temple that
they worshiped at made out of this High
spin superconducting element
so moving right along
here we are now I need to dispel some
myths and maybe make some definitions
for everybody as we as we move on into
our into the presentation I'm sure many
of you have heard the term either arms
or ormus
and I want to stress that we did a lot
all of this where well most of this work
without ever hearing the name Dave
Hudson and his work on white powder of
gold how many people are familiar with
that
many many people I see in the audience
through the bright lights
um
we did all of our work independent of
This research hardly even hearing of the
name
we didn't hear we didn't understand the
word monoatomic we didn't know the word
monoatomic which stands for single atom
element
that's actually a misnomer his white
powder of gold was never monoatomic
which brings us to the last the last
phrase arms stands for orbitally
rearranged monoatomic elements
also a misnomer because all of these
elements are not monoatomic they are in
fact diatomic
instead we called the elements that we
were working with
we call them high spin elements
and I'll be explaining what that means
we called them etheric elements
and
we call them organic elements what's the
difference between the car that you
drive drove here today in and the iron
found in the vegetables that you had
last night for dinner
they're they've gone through a different
process and so we worked with elements
that we called organic because the body
could absorb them they could be readily
absorbed by the body
now let me whoop
we've got a lot of energy flowing around
here buttons getting pushed machines
generating energy it's kind of fun but
plays havoc with computers okay what we
have here is a model of the solar system
and this is a this is an interesting
example when I talk about high spin
elements and by the way I'm I'm speaking
I'm speaking to uh I'm trying to convey
these words in the terms that everybody
can understand I'm not trying to speak
in quantum physics lingo because a lot
of you wouldn't understand what's going
on so I'm I'm I want to convey this in a
in a basically scientific but very easy
to understand manner now what we have
here is a model of the solar system and
in here we have mercury which orbits at
a at a time period of about 58 days
around the Sun okay very very quickly
it's moving very fast
we have at the outer end of the solar
system
Pluto which orbits at a rate of about
248 years around the sun which by the
way it was not until
1998 it was not the uh the furthest
planet out it was actually inside the
orbit of Neptune but that's beside the
fact now imagine that you were to take
an element let us say since we'll be
talking about the element gold let's say
gold and you were to expanded out to the
size of the solar system what you would
find was that the nucleus was was
actually would actually be somewhat
larger than the size of the sun
and that the outermost electrons would
be spinning out beyond the orbit of
Pluto
that is in conventional metal to metal
metal to metal gold
now imagine this in a high spin State
those electrons which are spinning out
very very uh very very relatively slowly
are suddenly pulled in somewhere inside
the orbit of Venus or the Earth
they still have all that momentum they
still have all that energy but now
they're spinning much much faster
spinning around the uh as close to the
surface of the Sun
this is an example
it's not entirely accurate but it is an
example to illustrate what is going on
in high spin elements
oops let me go back not ready yet
okay
they told me that I couldn't tell any
jokes but this was my this was my
attempt pitiful attempt at humor as we
we've all seen Fantasia if you can
imagine that these bubbles are in fact
the electrons so spinning around the
nucleus of the atom and these elephants
are the nucleus or the belly button of
the atom and the faster the elephants
Spin The Closer
those electrons come to the elephants
come to the nucleus of the atom that's a
my humorous nod to uh
to uh an illustration so we're going to
have a quick video here
and I'm going to demonstrate how I
mentioned that these elements are
actually what are called type 3
superconductors Dr Lawrence Gardner has
defined type 3 as basically room
temperature superconductors our next
slide is going to illustrate that oh wow
they're still dancing let's get rid of
that shall we
one more time there we go okay
wait can we pause that
okay video was shot on July 25th 1996 on
my kitchen table
okay the almost gold was made from
metallic gold chloride using ozone watch
the video the only materials used were
commercial gold chloride salt
hydrochloric acid bicarbonate of soda
distilled water and ozone
I am placing the ormus gold on a piece
of paper which has been folded to make
it more rigid I will be moving a rare
earth magnet around under the paper and
the pile of warmest gold will respond to
the magnet this is my good friend Barry
Carter
the rare earth magnet came from Radio
Shack here I am holding the magnet in my
fingers so you can get a better idea of
its relative size
watch the small pile of ormus gold as I
start to move the magnet under it
notice that the ormus gold powder is
following the magnet
ordinary gold is well known for not
being attracted to magnets
several gold mining methods take
advantage of this fact by separating the
heavy magnetic materials from the gold
using a magnet
this magnetic material is generally
discarded on the mine site
notice how the ormus gold appears to
build up a charge from the magnet moving
under it until it reaches some sort of
charged state where it is repelled by
the magnet and jumps away from it
now remember that he mentioned that this
was formed with the use of ozone we'll
be talking about that later on this is
uh one of the emergent technologies that
are coming out of the study of ormus
powder are ormus elements rather
and I I like to use the word high spin
rather than ormus just because I I
believe it's more accurate description
of the elements that we're working with
hmm
all right yeah
no this
is good thank you
all right
um while we're watching this these
elements are found in many many
locations for instance Black Sands is a
is a readily available source of these
types of elements leading to work done
with with charging Water by placing them
into a bit large Vats of Black Sands
they can be Black Sands are also used to
as a source for different types of
minerals that leads the minerals out and
then you actually can take the minerals
and as a supplement
you know what I'm going to leave Barry
behind now as we move on to the next
stage
these elements over here if we can turn
on the lights a little bit again these
elements are also examples of blacks of
uh of of high spin elements this right
here is a very interesting Rock
um
literally at one point in time
there was a vein if you can imagine
there was a vein of this
and a uh a blast of molten metal shot
through the vein and crystallized on the
metal what we have is a is a this is
actually kind of a poor example but we
have a peacock color on this
and what happens is that this was
volatized and was joined to this and
we'll be talking a little bit about more
ore processing later on however I want
to point out that
when you process this out depending on
what type of processes you use you get
different values out so if you go
through a regular
regular metal or assay you may show
nothing but if you take it through
another process for instance one that
uses maybe electricity or pressure you
get some type of values out
so these these uh High spin elements are
very very touchy they don't respond very
well to normal chemistry and so you have
to be very careful when you're when
you're actually dealing with them that
you don't just volatize them off and
make them all go away
let's move on to the next place
okay if we can turn the lights down we
can see this a little bit better this is
an exam more examples for those of you
who can't see down here to the front
this is this this is the white stone
that I am speaking of the white stone
that that Temple site was actually made
out of
and right below it is another Temple
site that was very very educational to
us
excuse me and I'll be getting into it if
you can imagine that uh regular matter
has three legs in our reality okay three
legs in our existence and once again
there are quantum physics terms that I
could use to describe this but I'm not
going to
types three High spin superconductors
have instead of free legs in this
reality
they have two in the physical I'm
sipping out of the light again they have
two in the physical and one in the
etheric OR Quantum reality literally for
a time period they are
all the way into the other reality back
into ours
and this ancient Society whichever
ancient Society built that Temple before
uh they understood this this is
literally a pictogram and this is a very
interesting story this is actually a
quite an amazing adventure
um this uh this is the beginning
pictograms at a temple site in southern
here in southern Utah actually
and this is actually All That Remains we
were led to this Temple site to learn
how to make what we call etheric
Elements and I'll be defining that in
just a moment
we were led to this Temple site to learn
how to make those elements and shortly
thereafter within one year of us going
there
taking pictures and decoding the
pictograms and the language
the temple site was nearly completely
destroyed as if it was waiting just just
for the moment that we needed to be
there
to uh to learn what was left
well recently I was able to actually go
back to that Temple site and drink and
take in the elements as they did
anciently it was a quite quite a quite a
wonderful experience let me decode this
really quick before we go on and I want
to stress before before I start doing
this that in this language their written
language there were at least three
different ways to read their written
language
one was the secular informational
one was their spiritual or religious and
one was their technological all right
and so we found plates where literally
you read them in a spiral
and which pictogram or glyph you start
with dictates whether or not you're
reading for the physical the spiritual
or the scientific
now this this pictogram right here we
have the the pictogram this is archaic
Hebrew by the way
the archaic Hebrew pictogram for gold it
also stands for written or record
we have a vessel
which this was approximately eight yards
from a blast furnace that was so hot The
Rock was literally melted and pulled at
the bottom that had been so hot that The
Rock was melted and pooled at the bottom
so we believe that that's actually where
they melted it at one point we have a
very interesting symbol here
and I'll be going more into this later
on it is the of course the figure eight
we know it as an as basically an
infinity symbol also and a magnetic
field
now anybody recognize this little symbol
maybe from this little device right here
I'll be showing that a little later on
and then we have the arcade or excuse me
the classical Egyptian symbol for
eternal life the Ankh
Now red altogether basically this is
talking about taking gold and putting it
through a process this is the uh this is
the archaic Hebrew symbol for the word
mouth
and taking basically taking gold through
a process into your body
for life
so we get to start to get a clue and
understanding of what these ancients
used these elements for
and this out they're they're not very
many pieces there left but there are
similar pieces to that crystalline Rock
there little shards and fragments found
around that Blast Furnace that are still
there that haven't been picked away
lastly
I want you to find the term etheric now
in some of the other lectures I was
really fascinated because they were
talking about things like dark matter
and dark energy
Dr Thurston uh
Ludwig from uh from Germany was talking
about this and it was interesting that
he said a 70 30 split Giver tank this is
a picture well a radio scopic image of a
black hole now as you'll see there is
something
actually coming out
escaping from the black hole and we met
a gentleman recently by the name of
well we hope his name is there
okay that would be great
oh okay that's why I can't scroll
forward here
there we go oh that's fantastic
now this is very interesting we'll be
going into more into this later because
essentially what we're seeing is matter
escaping from a black hole now we've
always been told that black holes have
such a high gravitational density that
not even light can escape from it and so
uh Dr John milewski formerly of uh
formerly of NASA and Los Alamos has
defined this as what is called super
luminous light now literally there are
just as a side note there are thousands
and thousands of these black holes
emitting the super luminous light and it
literally comes through into our
atmosphere and it is life-giving energy
I'll be going more into that later on as
we as we progress here
and this is where we came to on what we
came to understand was in fact etheric
elements what that Temple site that we
just visited taught us how to make
but these elements are a little bit
different they in fact have one leg in
our physical reality and they have two
legs in the etheric OR Quantum reality
this is very interesting because they
can be tasted on the tongue you can
measure them with an with a total
dissolved solids meter they change the
conductivity of water and yet gone
through a x-ray spectrograph they are
invisible
it's quite interesting
we'll also see how later on how they are
under certain circumstances how they are
not affected by gravity
this is a symbol once again
back to the temple site these two
symbols which are which are very
interesting to us uh well they're all
interested what
okay thank you
um
it's very interesting if you decode
these two symbols the archaic Hebrew and
then the classical Egyptian if you take
their two their two meanings and put
them together literally you get the
phrase to pass over
which is very interesting if you study
the works of people like Lawrence
Gardner and such when they talk about
the uh the the Passover bread what was
that exactly what was the Egyptian cone
bread
right next to it we have a symbol but
you're wondering what that is that is
the
um a little bit later age than that this
is the uh Egyptian symbol for the word
gold
and so when we put them all together
see the correlation there literally to
pass over
we have gold here
and
Robert Patterson's Ram implosion Wing
now it was interesting last year he
talked about how this implosion Wing
would eventually have to be made out of
a superconductor well what do we have
here
but a room temperature type 3
superconductor
and it is in fact High spin gold
that has been gone through a process
like it talked about on the other page
and so our net one of our next uh
one of our next subjects of research is
to actually make one of these wings out
of that high spin element
now I want to talk a little bit about
what
about what type of elements have been
found to to be able to be put in the
high spin State and these have been
found to be able to be put in there
because they've actually been put in to
find them in nature is actually very
difficult because as I mentioned before
some of them many of them are actually
spectroscopically invisible so what you
have to do is you have to look for
markers for instance goal a monatomic or
high spin gold is actually found in
areas of uh of large doses of aluminum
silicate and so you can set when you
find that element you can separate this
out and utilize it Cobalt
has been found to be in a high-spin
state I'm just going to run through some
of these very quickly nickel copper
which
if you get on the the website subtle
energies.com you can actually see before
and after pictures of people taking
etheric copper where gray beards have
gone completely Brown again that type of
thing ruthenium ruthenium is actually
being used in conventional science and
conventional DNA research and I'll be
getting to that in just a few minutes
rhodium which is a high spin rhodium is
actually one of the major ingredients in
your mind
rhodium along with iridium
Palladium is also very important silver
when silver is is put into a high-spin
state
it becomes an even better
bacteriological or a bacteria killer
than regular colloidal silver which is
in fact can be in fact very bad for you
you don't want to take that because you
get a whole lot of you can get heavy
metal poisoning
renium osmium now osmium for those of
you in the mining industry osmium knows
that are that they know that osmium is
in fact very very dangerous to the body
if you smell the uh the garlic smell
when you're working with ore you're in
pretty much really big trouble
um osmium will destroy regular osmium
will destroy gold it will take it up and
evaporate it'll be all gone
but
High spin osmium is in fact
not does not have in fact those effects
iridium once again is is utilized inside
of your brain
and that is all there's also research
being done in anti-gravity with iridium
but that's uh kind of the scientific
urban legend the interesting thing is
though that the emerging countries that
are putting uh putting satellites in
orbit they're also buying up huge
amounts of iridium from well just about
any iridium mine they can get a hold of
Platinum also has very interesting
properties Heating and Cooling gold as
we'll get into and Mercury now this is a
Mercury is is often used in alchemical
references but that's another field of
field of study that we don't really need
to get into right at this time
in our quest to understand what these
how these elements work and what they do
in the body
we were actually led to the work of
Victor schauberger and excuse me every
uh some of his defining work was done
with counter rotating vortices in water
and he was a for those of you don't know
he was able to transport water vast
distances he was able to to actually
transport water vast distances very very
quickly he was able to purify water
using using vortices and such even to
the point of desalination I've actually
met a gentleman in Texas if anybody has
ever heard heard of uh
what's that
Joseph
Bender yes thank you he has created
water that is so wet that you could hold
it in your hand and watch it absorb into
your skin and water that is so dry that
no matter how much you drank of it you
would die of dehydration
are using the schauberger vortices okay
and if anybody finds him he uh I'd like
to talk to him again but he seems to
have disappeared
now what we have here is now I mentioned
that I mentioned that ormists are
assuming High spin elements are found in
in many locations and I should probably
talk about that a little bit more
um one of the one of the highest found
locations is as I said Black Sands
another location is any place where
there is salt so oceans Dead Sea we have
this Great Salt Lake up here which a lot
of people are pulling these high spin
elements out problem is you have to be
very very careful because unless you are
a master chemist you will also drop out
heavy metals and if you don't up if you
don't operate within a very limited
range pH balance you will drop out heavy
chemicals and a lot of people that we
found that take High spin elements or
Miss elements per se they in fact have
heavy metal aluminum poisoning so you
have to watch out for that
aluminum
and silica are not the same thing as
aluminum silicate aluminum and silica
does not equal
monatomic or high spin gold okay
remember that
well what they eventually found was that
all water has this and even Victor
schauberger talked about it in his work
he actually mentioned that if you store
water in a Flats in a flat Lake and such
something in that water dies and what we
have found in our research is that the
thing that happens to the water is that
all of the the living High spin elements
start to evaporate off because they
don't like the sunlight they don't like
to be just directly exposed to the
sunlight and they don't like the
stagnant water something dies there and
so utilizing these these counter
rotating vortices he was able to
re-energize water
so some of the people in the in the uh
the high spin element research decided
to
take Victor schauberger's vortices work
and try to create a trap can we focus it
can we concentrate these elements enough
how am I doing on time
you've got about
almost 30 minutes okay great great okay
let me let me show you what this trap is
here this is called enormous trap it
wastes a lot of water I don't actually
recommend this trap at all but anyway
what happens is you have water flowing
in through a hose and it starts to swirl
down this pipe there's it goes in at an
angle so that the whole thing swirls
down this pipe there is a block here at
this end with a cone on it so that the
so that what you do is you create a
counter rotating vortices instead of
instead of letting that travel on you
create a counter rotating field of water
that is that instead travels back up the
tube
when it reaches this other end there is
a filter per se of
Pardon Me
there's a filter of a cloth that only
allows oil to pass through it's a very
interesting material however when you
concentrate High spin elements like this
when you concentrate the ormus in the
water in this manner essentially the
water literally becomes oily and it can
pass through that cloth and flow out
through this tube where it's collected
now I want to tell you an interesting
experience
right after I drink some water
since
absolutely water is life
what is that Dune I think okay
we and we instead instead of making this
which actually wastes a lot of water we
decided to make a a pot trap now I want
to stress this is independent of our
Research into electric water magnetic
water and high spin elements this was uh
for just for informational purposes so
we could further understand what we were
working with
we made this pot trap which is
essentially this stretched into a larger
area the water comes in through the top
begins to spin and form a a vortices
here or assuming a spinning Whirlpool
essentially here in the top of this uh
trap there are magnets placed inside
here and at the base about right here
the water spins and Spins and Spins now
one thing about magnets magnets as we
met as we saw earlier in the uh in the
uh jumping ormus video by Barry Carter
magnets irritate or stimulate the flow
and I thought that was very interesting
in some of the other speakers they have
in their presentations they have been
talking about pulsing magnets and to
stimulate a response now I'll be getting
to that because it's amazing how uh it's
amazing how everything ties in together
isn't it last year the buzzword was
implosion everybody was using it this
year it's it's something different
anyway
these magnets stimulate the high spin
elements in the water and there is a
trap basically in the base here and I
can we can show pictures of this at my
present at my table when we're done here
but it was too much to go into in this
um what happened was we had a we have a
well and we just started flushing the
water through this into a holding tank
which we ran down to our to our bath
house into our greenhouse and such so we
weren't actually wasting any water
but what happened was we let this sit
for about three weeks and the ormus
material in the that collected in the
base here became incredibly concentrated
there was an accident the pot was
knocked over we'd learned what we needed
to learn about about high spin elements
in water at that point anyway and we put
the pots back into use in the kitchen
now what was very interesting was this
one day we had to uh
um evaporate off a bunch of wet salts
that we were that we were that we were
using in something and we put the salt
the wet salt into this stainless steel
pot actually it was the internal
stainless steel pot not this pot but the
internal one that was actually holding
the high spin ormus water
we put the salt in there set it on the
counter just to you know evaporate the
water off what was interesting within
three days
salt was found on the counter it was not
bubbling out of the top of the it was
not evaporating out of the top of the
pot it was literally growing out the
sides of the pot I believe the quantum
physics term is Josephson tunneling I
think is that right
okay literally the plot had become its
own superconductor and the salt was
growing out the sides of that
now that is very interesting because
when you start looking at the idea that
well there didn't seem to be any salt
taken out of the pot it was just growing
out the sides and literally it covered
the counter within about 10 inches
so there's a lot of applications to this
um but we'll get to those we'll get to
those
what we also what we have here is
um I want I want to define the organic
elements term that we used by that we
mean we meant they could be dissolved in
water
and they can be absorbed by the body
well what was interesting about Dave
Hudson's work and I actually met Dave
Hudson's chemist for those of you who
don't know his name is Don Duke it's a
very interesting fellow and he talked
about a 32-step process where they took
the
the high spin gold that they were
collecting off the ground and eventually
turned it into the metal to metal gold
and then turned it into
High spin gold again and he himself was
was uh
um was working on that process now the
problem was that you had to take massive
amounts of the of the material for your
body to absorb even the tiniest tiniest
bit
and so what we what we've worked with
and once again this was done without
even hearing about Dave Hudson as a
matter of fact after shortly after this
work that was when shortly after this
work right here was when we first found
uh found out about Dave Hudson and Don
Duke came to our house and we kind of
blew him away with that right there
um
this is organic rhodium and iridium it
comes from from a plant Source goes
through several processes the developer
of this
who stumbled onto it calls it operiori
which is which is an old term it means
to know without experience
and when that it's actually greenish
powder you can't actually see it there
when that is put into water
what you get is this beautiful Violet
liquid
that's organic rhodium iridium now
remember I said rhodium and iridium is
one of the primary components of your
brain
and when you take this into your into
your body in conjunction with something
else that we'll talk about in a few
minutes
you have incredibly increased mental
awareness all sorts of things happen
that we won't go into at this time but
we can talk about it at the table if you
guys want to visit after the
presentation
what we have here on this side
is a white uh is a white high spin
element gold and goes when you take it
through another process you get to this
right here now this is very interesting
because this is in fact
um used in something that we call an
etheric battery
and it is absolutely essential to some
of the processes that we work with
white nephew okay go for that please let
me find out where I'm at here
okay I want to also stress once again
that these elements are found in many
many locations uh Dr John milewski that
I've mentioned earlier
lives in lives in Arizona he believes
that the white deposits oops that's okay
that's okay we'll just move on he
believes that the white deposits found
on the rocks in the area that collects
there overnight after a rainstorm that
type of thing is in fact the high spin
the high spin elements falling
distilling out of the air
and once again they're also attracted to
anywhere there's salt so if you can find
also salt deposits buried in the ground
for instance Redmond salt that type of
thing you're you're on the trail of high
spin elements
now what we have here is how these
organic L I want to talk about how these
organic elements interact with the body
and in living systems what we have here
on the right
is a I read backwards a lot
it comes from studying archaic Hebrew so
things end up on the right and then move
to the left sometimes what we have here
are conventional walnuts
that are about the same size as any as
regular walnuts
this tree was treated with was basically
fertilized with the high spin elements
and for for one year and the next year
the elements are assuming the walnuts
were much much larger than they were
before same tree same amount of water
the only difference is the high SP is
the high spin elements now we can go
into a whole subject of Agriculture
using these high spin elements they have
done work creating trees that are corn
corn stalks that are 15 feet tall give
or take
some of the research that we have done
has produced uh turnips that are about
10 pounds and five pound carrots stuff
like that really quite amazing using uh
using these ormus elements in
conjunction with an energy form with
basically etheric energy we'll be
talking about that in a minute so
essentially fruits and vegetables grow
faster and larger than
um than they do without without this
type of uh stimulation because they
really really need it now let me talk
about gold in the use of Agriculture
really quickly
um so friends of mine met a gentleman
who was richer than sin just had a lot
of money to throw around and he had
heard that gold will stimulate plant
growth so instead of trying these little
experiments
he went out and built himself a
greenhouse of pounded gold foil now it's
very expensive it's the same stuff they
use on on the astronaut's face Shields
so really expensive stuff he pound gold
flat out to a molecule thick you can see
through it but it reflects certain
amounts of uh radiation and stuff like
that it's an excellent filter he created
an entire Greenhouse like this and he
was also getting this type of response
he did not have tomato plants he had
tomato trees and things like that
so the applications here are tremendous
okay there's a reason why people have
people have desired and wanted gold
since the beginning of time as a matter
of fact I was in a as an interesting
side note I was in a room with some
gentleman and they received their assay
from their mind and their assay was a
huge amount of of rhodium and iridium
and platinum and very very little gold
and they threw the assay down on the
table and by the way at the time rhodium
was around 900 an ounce iridium 12. gold
was maybe 250. and they threw this assay
down on the table and discussed and says
I don't want platinum and rhodium and
iridium I want gold well for crying out
loud there was a Much More Much More
Much More values in the rhodium and
iridium but there's a reason why people
desire the gold and we'll be getting to
that in conventional research
oh I've mentioned the organic rhodium
and iridium found in the brain now we
did some very interesting research with
that
utilizing uh the electric water that
I've been talking about at the table out
there and that beautiful purple liquid
that I talked that we that I showed on
the screen
you take that into your body and in very
interesting things happen inside of your
brain you start having
incredible memory you start having
incredibly lucid dreams and the stories
go on from there we can talk about that
outside now I want to I want to stress
that most of the things I'm talking
about this in particular
this is not anecdotal this is personal
experimental experience okay we did this
we did this work it wasn't somebody else
so I can so everything I'm talking about
with this
was uh is is personal testimony okay
lastly this is conventional research by
the way ruthenium I mentioned that it
has been used in DNA research
they take ruthenium and they put a
single ruthenium molecule right there or
excuse me ruthenium element atom that's
the word Adam right there and right
there at the end of a DNA structure and
you know what it does to the DNA
turns the DNA into a superconductor
the DNA cannot reproduce wrong because
all of the information all of the
information is communicated back and
forth exactly
in other in other convention this this
is conventional research in other
conventional research they do the same
thing with Platinum
they put Platinum here and platinum here
and what happens is that the DNA strand
unwinds and lays flat and then begins to
wind in a manner that is very very
conducive to to healthy regeneration
that's conventional research their
problem is that they can't figure out
how to put the the atoms on the end of
every single molecule in your body but
it's actually quite simple when you go
into the high spin State because they
naturally migrate to where they need to
be anyway and we'll be talking about
that with the water in just a moment
here is gold in the body how many of you
have ever had any work done with dark
field microscopy raise your hand
okay dark field Micron okay wow there we
go not very many but some okay thank you
you can turn that down now so we can see
the screen appreciate that guys
okay what we have here is a dark field
microscopy video of a live blood cell
now there are a lot of things that can
go wrong and uh with with taking a live
blood cell analysis but they can be very
very accurate in certain ways you don't
have to kill the blood you don't have to
stain the blood you're literally looking
at a holographic representation about
what's going on in the body so dark
field microscopy dark field microscopy
or live blood analysis in conjunction
with with the dry layer technique can
tell you
massive amount of things about your body
about what's going on inside of you
unfortunately it doesn't translate very
well to pictures
you need to see it on a moving video
screen in order to really see what's
going on but basically we have what we
have are these cells these are your red
blood cells and this is actually very
unhealthy blood see the the misshapen
blood see how it's uh see how it's
bulged out and star patterns bottle caps
you want to see some because that's
normal but this person has problems well
these little spots right here
and some of them are and some of them
aren't you can only tell if they're
moving
but these little spots are in fact what
are called Regulators or protists or
there's numerous names for them they are
the communicators and digesters of the
body when in a proper pH these run
around and clean off the outside of your
cells they communicate back and forth to
different areas of the body they tell
the white blood cells hey we just had a
scrape and it's totally infected go to
that spot right now and all the white
blood cells run there which are by the
way they're dual nuclei cells they're
also T cells so you increase your immune
system boost up your uh boost up the the
T cell count and naturally of course not
by getting sick and you basically become
more and more taking steps toward
becoming immortal
oh thank you
moving right along
gold what we found in these in this in
our research in our in our particular
research was that gold is in fact the
PowerHouse of the blood
the more
High spin elements gold you have in your
body the less these basically break down
and destroy your body and the more they
the more they actually help and rebuild
and regenerate re-energize your body
and the the father of modern dark field
microscopy Dr enderlein actually calls
these Regulators in the blood which as I
said relate to the amount of ormus or uh
high-spin element gold that you have in
your body he calls them the colloids of
Light which beget the colloids of life
without these we die okay it's just that
simple in space research
let me talk about magnetic fields really
quick and then I'll get into the space
research
um
what's that
oh okay sorry
um
what we have here are pictures of the
magnetic fields of the earth and if we
have enough time I'll tell you a little
secret about magnetic fields that are
that really really benefits anybody that
does any research in uh well let's say
magnetic motors and such but what we're
talk what we're looking at here is the
magnetic fields of the Earth and when we
started measuring them approximately
eighteen hundreds 1900s the field was
about 13 Gauss
now the field is down to 0.3 Gauss
there's a number of reasons why that's
happening huge debate over it but we
know that it is happening we estimate
that at the time of those temples were
built and such the core samples show
that the the
magnetic field was up over a thousand
gals
now what happens in the body when when
the magnetic field goes to zero living
living systems need desperately need
magnetic fields
and this is the Dr Dean bonnelly's work
if you want to look him up he created a
chamber that they could lower the
magnetic field to zero essentially the
first stage the mice spontaneously
developed Cancers and tumors that
normally only only happen when they are
injected by toxins
second stage they had memory loss upon
dissection they had all the symptoms
they had all the problems of Alzheimer's
and third stage they had spontaneous
death now is that happening in the world
today
okay magnetic fields are very important
to living systems oops
what's that
they will go through the reversal after
they after they drop to zero they stay
at zero for three days if you do not
have a magnetic field in those three
days there's a high possibility you will
either die or lose your memory
as evidenced by the mice and and other
evidence
archaeological evidence too by the way
okay
when you Char I'm running out of time
here so I had to skip a little bit I'd
be happy to talk to everybody about some
of the other potentials of these
um out in the lobby after the uh after
the presentation when you charge what or
excuse me when you charge energy
with these etheric elements now I
personally believe I don't know how many
people were here for the presentation
that they were talking about uh Dr Moray
and how and his uh and his um
and the elements that he used in his
tubes I personally believe that these
were the elements that he originally
used before he went into the the uh the
radioactive materials because of the
work that we have that we have done when
you couple the etheric energy generated
by these
um by these elements with regular
electricity
and run them through water literally the
water will hold a magnetic field
it becomes very beneficial to the body
and your spirit I have a buddy who
drinks uh this electric water solely for
the purpose of controlling his temper
because he has a violent temper and when
he drinks about an ounce he's able to
control it so it has something to do
with the magnetic field on the body
so what we have done is essentially
coupled
etheric energy we stimulate
the elements that you see there on the
table
and get a response back now this ties in
very well with some of the other
lectures that have been presenting here
because they are talking about pulsing
with a magnetic field get a response
stimulating or irritating and getting a
response
oh
and lastly we've had very very
interesting temporal dilation effects
with this but we can talk about that out
at the uh out at the booth the future
research
anyone who's doing any research in
things like anti-gravity
can benefit from researching these
elements the reason why as I mentioned
earlier etheric elements or super
luminous light as Dr mileski calls it
under certain circumstances
Coast with an elect excuse me pulse with
a magnetic and pulsed electrical field
not an electrical magnetic AC field but
a magnetic and a pulsed DC field these
elements exhibit anti-gravity tendencies
so these propulsion devices and such
they would if utilizing utilizing DC
pulses is really fantastic
um once again propulsion if you have
lift you can also have propulsion some
people believe that the doctor and now
his name is completely slipped my mind
the doctor in Russia that is doing
anti-gravity
research some of them believe that the
elements that he's using are in fact
these high spin type 3 superconductors
and coils
or working or processing
you need to study these because your
assay for instance the Russian assay is
done in high temperature and
inert gases show one thing but when you
process it out nothing shows up
you need to study why that is happening
and and how to manipulate these to get
out what you want
time dilation effects there are numerous
reports of these even in my own personal
experience
one time
driving with someone who had was very
much charged up on these and we made a
trip that takes six hours and this is
honest truth took us two and a half
hours no speeding whatsoever because of
the mind's interaction with these high
spin elements
and lastly Health and Longevity we we
personally are working on research on
how to extend life
and excuse me
and find out why the body ages how and
how we can stop the breakdown how we can
promote regeneration
so any questions
are we about done
thank you
okay we have uh
that was from 2005. what a great
presentation and that's just a sample of
what you can see at our conferences and
note
how he kept referring to his table for
people who had more more questions and
answers and need some answers
um that's the importance of the
conference I encourage all of you to uh
uh consider uh coming to this year's
conference I think it's going to be a
great conference
uh unfortunately Vern is no longer with
us uh as far as I come to our
conferences we hope to see him come back
one of these days it's been about a good
five years I believe and um
and I hope you know maybe he might have
time this year to show up or maybe he
might even do a paper he's a talented a
researcher and a great presentation
um so um
that's about all I got does anyone have
any questions to shoot over the comments
I'll keep my eyes open there
um
and let me uh go ahead and leave you
with uh
some words from uh Greg has it been
going on for more than 40 years 25
speakers or more each year so that's
like a thousand or more of these
presentations you can get and the fact
is a lot of these guys are inventors and
they had you know stuff that they have
been showing this is the place where
they come to show and tell and many of
them are passed away and so the only
place you can go to recover what they
gave us what they gave to the world is
teslotech magnetic motors water Theory
and inventors uniquely displaying that
great inventions over 50 years of the
greatest Minds you have Royal Rife who
invented the rife microscope Google them
you have John Keeley he was not a
charlatan Victor schomberger another
brilliant mind specialized in vertical
lift my name is Marco Rhoden I'm the
discoverer of The Deco qubit I just
completed a four hour workshop and it is
available for you if you subscribe to
Tesla Tech I was playing around with
these rodent numbers but then I realized
there's an application a really cool one
one I've been working on for 10 years
and that's basically an electron model I
can I can model these numbers like their
frequencies in in the next Direction a y
direction a z Direction and they roll
back into themselves the model is
amazing it's three-dimensional it has
all the properties I've been looking for
for an electron model I'm very excited
about it you're talking about Giants and
free energy
Fusion Electronics mathematics esoteric
knowledge you must check this out it's a
subscription only rightly so because
you're talking about wisdom that you
can't find anywhere on the internet
breakthroughs or discoveries videos that
you'll never find find anywhere else my
name is Mon and I come from Georgia I've
been coming with family and friends to
the Tesla convention for almost 10 years
the most prized possession was coming
back home to Georgia with the CDs so
when I just found out that all this
material is available on YouTube for uh
for a subscription we can go on YouTube
we can subscribe we can sit together
chat
people this conference about this is a
great channel for only 9.99 you get the
legends of this field and you'll find
the greatest array and world's biggest
assortment of free energy over Unity
Zero Point Energy space Power propulsion
medical Counter Culture breakthrough
technology all hosted there it's the
largest video library ever assembled
live on very good video takes and you
can get involved you can be part of this
process right emails have direct contact
with with the speakers and guess what if
you're truly inspired for what you see
over there next year you can join us
[Music]
well uh once again
I like people to sign up for the
conference uh we still have a 30
discount till next week you know so uh
you sign up as soon as you can and Maria
asked us if um
if I remember what he said was a secret
to magnetic fields
I don't think he got back to that I
think he just ran out of time you know
because he covers a lot of material and
uh Vernon has a lot of uh videos up on
our uh
on our uh channel here so uh just go to
testatech.info and look up uh Verona and
Roth you know in the speaker directory
and yeah you see him all that we have up
there right now and we have more to come
and we even have auxilia
videos that that would be relate like he
talks about David Husband well we also
have the Global Science conference
videos up there uh up to 95 I think
maybe 96 and uh we'll be putting more up
there in a couple weeks so when I get
more time and um
and David Hudson is among among them so
you're getting good source material to
build on this okay and uh
and I can't encourage people enough to
just go out and uh come to the
conference
become uh meet the guys okay I think um
I I think him he'll walk away with a
friend that much I could probably I
could probably give a written guarantee
that you're going to meet someone who
you um
can connect with you know because the
people come to this conference are
unique uh
a subset of this our population people
talk to me well there's like a
300 million people in the country or
whatever uh and uh we should be getting
a lot more millions of people well
the people who think are really
interested in this are so intelligent
okay and wide range and and what they do
and they connect a lot of different
fields and that is not really a common
aspect of the general population or any
population
but anyway with that
um I just do want to make one more note
um
and that is when uh Vern was talking
about these uh vast civilizations you
know that we have no records of
well look at our society and all we're
converting more and more of our uh our
resources our records to electronic
means and that and we're getting rid of
paper
and so what I if a civilization has come
along okay and look at our civilization
and
they didn't have the device you needed
to actually read the record
um
doesn't mean that the records aren't
there it just means that
we don't have the technology to actually
access them
um
right now I try to keep I I try to have
some kind of written record whenever
possible but it's just impossible
um
and someday I hope you get my magazine
up and running again I'm working on it
right now
and in our programs I like sitting on
our programs uh I already got this
year's program printed
um and I'd say you'll be getting that in
the mail soon so I am
definitely after Memorial Day uh we'll
be able to get an entrepreneur more of
that I think
and uh
just for a preview I'm not sure who I'm
going to have for next week or what I'm
gonna do uh it's kind of a short notice
at this point but uh the week after
um
okay we will be in um
and Indian Wells at the contact in the
desert conference I come visit us at the
table there we'll have a table there uh
and that will be uh from June 1st uh
this is the third I believe you know I
need to just I'll put something up on
the Internet before I leave uh or before
next week and let you know um uh what's
going on and where it's going to be at
if you're in the neighborhood you might
want to check it out but that's where
I'll be so I I won't have a show
on the week after next you know for sure
uh the next
sure I would definitely have
will be in June
um June 11th and uh
I'm hoping to get some really super
speakers by by that anyway
um
uh coming to our conference sign up this
week if you can opt to get that 30 off
um
and if you
if you bring two if two more sign up
again extra five percent
yeah
and so uh that's a civil savings
and
if you have a
a big group give me a call maybe I can
make a arrangement for you to get you
get you all break if you're all sign up
for one time so anyway uh give me a call
my number is uh
520-463-1994 would be the office number
or you can call me on my show you know
I'll go ahead and take phone calls on my
cell because anyway
uh five two zero two five two zero three
seven four or go to testatech.info
um
and uh check us out
and you all have a great evening and uh
I'll be seeing you all
hopefully next week
so thank you
and that's gonna be a